[
  {
    "index": 1,
    "Question": "ふわふわ",
    "Answer": "fluffy",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 2,
    "Question": "もちもち",
    "Answer": "chewy",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 3,
    "Question": "ねばねば",
    "Answer": "sticky",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 4,
    "Question": "サラサラ",
    "Answer": "smooth",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 5,
    "Question": "水っぽい",
    "Answer": "watery",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 6,
    "Question": "ざらざら",
    "Answer": "rough",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 7,
    "Question": "つるつる",
    "Answer": "slippery",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 8,
    "Question": "カリカリ",
    "Answer": "crispy",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 9,
    "Question": "パリパリ",
    "Answer": "crunchy",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 10,
    "Question": "しっとり",
    "Answer": "moist",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 11,
    "Question": "ほろほろ",
    "Answer": "crumbly",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 12,
    "Question": "ぷりぷり",
    "Answer": "springy",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 13,
    "Question": "もろもろ",
    "Answer": "crumbly",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 14,
    "Question": "ごつごつ",
    "Answer": "bumpy",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 15,
    "Question": "ざくざく",
    "Answer": "coarse",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 16,
    "Question": "ぬるぬる",
    "Answer": "slimy",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 17,
    "Question": "ねちねち",
    "Answer": "tacky",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 18,
    "Question": "ふかふか",
    "Answer": "soft",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 19,
    "Question": "ざらざら感のある",
    "Answer": "grainy",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 20,
    "Question": "ゴワゴワ",
    "Answer": "stiff",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 21,
    "Question": "しなやか",
    "Answer": "supple",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 22,
    "Question": "こしがある",
    "Answer": "firm",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 23,
    "Question": "弾力がある",
    "Answer": "elastic",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 24,
    "Question": "かたく",
    "Answer": "hard",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 25,
    "Question": "やわらかい",
    "Answer": "soft",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  }
]